Please God.
He's still alive...
but slipped into a coma since
he's brain dead.
Alisha...
Welcome to the living world!
My love... if you're not mine,
I'll have no reason to live.
My love...
I'll always stay by your side.
My love... if you're not mine,
I'll have no reason to live.
My love...
I'll always stay by your side.
Can't live a moment without you...
Swear I'll fall apart.
Can't stop thinking about you
as long as I breathe...
You'll think of me even if I'm dead.
My love...
can't love anyone like I love you.
I'll always stay by your side.
My love... if you're not mine,
I'll have no reason to live.
You're my world...
My reason to be alive...
My love for you can never end.
You're my destination...
You're the journey...
You're the one that dwells in me.
You're my world...
My reason to be alive...
My love for you can never end.
You're my destination...
You're the journey...
You're the one that dwells in me.
I'll swim across...
I'll swim across the sea of love...
Let this night come again...
So for you I can sing...
Always stay by his side--
that's all I desire.
Happy Birthday to you!
It's a funeral, not a birthday,
you idiot!
Guess the old man left
a fortune behind.
Show some respect!
Respect--
The old man's dead and gone...
He lived and died for himself.
He was not some young kid--
Hey, idiot!
Have you lost your mind?
Not my mind...
My heart...
Zoom in the night like shhh
on a mission
Cape in the wind,
no fear, no permission
Took that hit?
Man, still I'm rise
Talk that talk,
but I live with precision.
Mask on face like a ghost in the mist
One clean punch,
now your crew don't exist
Broke your plan with
a flick of the wrist
Who did that little punk, you missed
Watch me fly like a glitch in the code
All black suit, that's a hero mode
Stare too long, you might just fold
Heart too pure but my soul too cold
I don't flex, but I will throw hands
No sidekick, I don't need no band
Don't need luck, just a slick game plan
Snap so hard they forgot
where they stand
Ronny, stop it!
That's how it is, sir.
He doesn't socialise or open up!
You should see how filthy his house is.
Though I live on the floor above him,
but he doesn't want
to be anywhere near me!
Dirty clothes! Dirty dishes!
Unwashed for weeks!
Yuck!
Why do you do it?
Honestly, some people make you wonder
why they died.
Then there are others
you wonder why they're still around.
What happened?
I was fighting with ten people alone,
while he was enjoying the view.
Brothers like you don't belong
in this world--
They belong in an underwear.
Where? In an underwear?
I should have been in an underwear?
What is he saying?
It's okay, calm down.
It's okay.
What can I say, sir?
Do you know what happened last night?
Take a look.
See...
Usually, it takes two to fight...
But you are throwing punches all alone.
So, who exactly are you fighting?
The accident and near death experience
has severely affected your brain.
What you think is real,
are actually hallucinations!
A figment of your imagination.
What about these bruises
I got during the fight?
Is this also my imagination?
Ronny... even I want all this
to be a dream.
I just hope everything goes
back to normal
and nothing ever goes wrong with you.
That's all.
If all this is a dream,
then I'm happy living
in my hallucination.
Oh, my God.
Ronny's condition...
His reactions...
his hallucination, anxiety...
It's like his mind's
playing tricks on him.
Some kind of trauma or tragedy--
Maybe an injury from his childhood,
or something that shook his heart.
Maybe someone else in his life...
Other than you?
I mean he's young, handsome.
Maybe a girl or relationship--
Sir, he keeps mentioning a girl
post his accident.
Someone called Alisha.
But there is no record of this Alisha.
No Pan Card, Aadhar Card,
Ration Card or passport...
Nothing.
If this Alisha existed,
I would have met her atleast once.
My love... if you're not mine,
I'll have no reason to live.
Sir, I think this Alisha only exists
in his mind.
Alisha doesn't exist in reality.
My love... if you're not mine,
I'll have no reason to live.
My love...
I'll always stay by your side.
Can't live a moment without you...
Swear I'll fall apart.
Can't stop thinking about you
as long as I breathe...
You'll think of me even if I'm dead.
My love...
can't love anyone like I love you.
I'll always stay by your side.
My love... if you're not mine,
I'll have no reason to live.
You're my world...
My reason to be alive...
My love for you can never end.
You're my destination...
You're the journey...
You're the one that dwells in me.
You're my world...
My reason to be alive...
My love for you can never end.
You're my destination...
You're the journey...
You're the one that dwells in me.
I'll swim across...
I'll swim across the sea of love...
I'm Olivia.
You're Ronny?
Attitude, huh!
Your brother has sent me
to make you happy.
He's always sending jobs
and girls my way.
Is he my brother or a p**p?
You have two hours.
Whatever you like...
But no kissing!
Whatever?
Whatever...
No... not this. I've never done this.
Dios Mio (Oh, God)!
This is new even for me.
What are you making me do, jerk?
Oh my God!
Son of a b***
what is this my God please.
Dios Mio (Oh, God)!
Why are you making me do this?
Bro said my house is unclean,
dishes are unwashed!
You said--
two hours... whatever!
I've had it!
Life just got flushed down the drain!
Billions of blue blistering barnacles
my youth has gone to the dogs!
Even they don't like what they got...
The audio doesn't match the video!
Why give Latinos a bad name
when you're from India?
You want me to give India
a bad name instead?
Small or large?
What's your name?
Olivia.
The one on your birth certificate.
Pratistha.
Meaning Honour.
But this name doesn't suit
our profession.
Taking your clothes
off doesn't damage your honour...
Nor does keeping them
on guarantee it stays intact.
It's in your mind.
Brilliant!
What an emotional statement.
These were her words.
The only person we talk about
behind their back
are the ones we like
Who is she?
Girlfriend?
Tell me!
Life seemed to begin with her...
and end with her.
That's amazing.
Introduce me to her someday.
She's no more!
Sorry.
We still have an hour left.
Tell me more about her.
Can't stop chanting your name...
from night to day...
You are the one who lights up my life.
So close am I to you...
I'm your good fortune ...
You are the one,
that shapes my destiny
Whether it's dusk or dawn.
you are always on my mind.
No matter what I do.
or where I go--
Your memory crossed my mind.
My heart's found relief.
I'll keep loving you...
to my last breath.
These distances say...
someday I'll make you mine.
This obsession... this insanity...
has got me high.
Whether it's dusk or dawn.
you are always on my mind.
No matter what I do...
or where I go--
Your memory crossed my mind.
My heart's found relief.
Love... is like a sea of fire.
But across I'll swim and not drown.
Yes, I am naive for falling in love...
Yes, I am guilty of loving you.
Love... is like a sea of fire.
But across I'll swim and not drown.
Yes, I am naive for falling in love...
Yes, I am guilty of loving you.
Your love... is my life!
Jeetu...
Where did you hide the photos?
Jeetu!
Where is my Alisha's album?
Jeetu, pick up the phone.
Pick up the phone, Jeetu!
Jeetu...
Can I share something with you?
I think of you as my son.
But I really hate that you've to
put with your lunatic brother's insanity.
He's crazy, son.
Take him to a mental hospital.
He's not crazy, aunty.
He's just a little edgy...
If this is what he does
when he's a little edgy...
What are you doing?
You think you can make me
forget about Alisha this way.
- What are you saying?
- Leave him.
I said leave him.
Aunty, one minute.
Please.
- Come with me.
- Stop stop...
- Ronny, what are you doing?
- I won't let you go!
Won't let you go!
Don't try to intimidate me.
You don't scare me.
Don't give me that stare!
You don't know...
- I will--
- What are you doing? Will you kill him?
Ronny, let her go.
Dear God!
He's coming after me.
Leave it, someone will get hurt!
I am going to die anyway.
Ronny, please.
Ronny...
Ronny, please drop it.
Ronny.
Aunty, get in!
Come with me.
He's your brother!
You don't hit your own brother,
you fool.
Go back inside, aunty.
Ronny, what are you doing?
Come with me.
But what happened, Ronny?
You think I am scared.
I'll see you soon...
Alisha's video was on it.
Where did it go?
What are you saying?
Which video?
Ronny, listen...
Listen to me.
Please, Ronny.
How did you end up
in the picture instead of Alisha?
Ronny, this picture has always been ours...
You are lying!
You can never replace Alisha!
I want the truth...
You called it hallucination,
I said nothing.
You sent a girl my way...
Again I said nothing!
Ronny, I think you're hallucinating again.
Hallucination...
Ronny, no.
- Ronny, stop it.
- You are behind all this.
Ronny, please stop it.
No, Ronny.
Where are my Alisha's pictures?
What are you doing, Ronny?
Stop it.
Ronny, please.
Ronny, calm down!
Stop, Ronny. For my sake.
Ronny...
just calm down.
You're the only family I have.
I can't see you like this, my brother.
Please...
Please.
Please. Calm down.
Ronny... Calm down.
Relax, my brother.
You're my life. Please.
It's just a figment of your imagination.
But everything will be alright.
It'll be okay.
- You called the police.
- No!
Ronny, no.
What do you mean wait.
I saw blood in his eyes.
There he is.
Dear God. Save me!
- That lunatic's got a hammer.
- Throw down the hammer!
- Ronny...
- Sir!
Please lower your gun, sir.
Please.
- Throw the hammar.
- He's my brother.
Throw it down!
It's a family matter, sir.
Ronny... put the hammer down.
- Jeetu, I brought them!
- Have you lost your mind, aunty?
Why did you call the police?
I will shoot you.
Throw it down.
Ronny... please...
Throw down the hammer, brother.
They are the cops, they will shoot!
Throw it down.
Throw it down!
Sir, sorry. Sorry.
I apologise, sir.
I apologise. Please forgive him.
Ronny, stop.
Sir, please. Ronny.
What are you doing?
Ronny, stop it.
Ronny, let them go.
Ronny no!
He attacked the ACP...
This is my introduction,
why do you get to throw the punch?
Hit me. Come on.
Hit me.
He will hit him.
I know it.
He hit me.
Your fingerprints are now
printed on my forehead.
Now watch my magic fingres.
Sir, can you stop tapping
on the table, please?
Why?
- Is it irritating?
- No...
I've had this habit...
Since childhood.
I am always tapping on something.
Of course, you are amazing at it.
Like a pro.
- Like it?
- Yes.
Get talking.
What is the problem here?
- Is it property?
- No, sir.
Kute...
At this age, hormones run wild
each pulling in different direction.
All this for a girl?
There is no girl, sir--
Low... keep it down...
Volume low...
- Am I not being polite?
- Yes, sir.
Talk like me.
- There is no girl--
- Hey!
In your own voice... low...
Low volume in my own voice?
Got it.
Speaking in low volume,
there is no girl, sir...
There is a girl.
How else can you explain her
dead body?
Sir...
It's okay, it's all good.
Wait...
what body?
And whose body?
Kute...
He said one body.
But everyone here is a dead body.
Yes, sir.
She's my Alisha.
Her?
Wow!
Girlfriend?
Nice.
Come, son. Take a look.
Aged girlfriend?
How is this possible?
Who is Margaret?
This is Alisha's grave.
Is this a grave or a parcel
which got switched?
Believe me... it's Alisha's grave.
See.
I wrote this.
- For Alisha!
- Okay.
You wrote this on Alisha's grave.
How did it end up on
Margaret's grave?
- Must be one of his plans!
- Mine?
- I've never been here in my life.
- Enough! Relax.
Kute... no girl, no body, no grave.
Pinch me. Am I even here?
Believe me, sir.
Why would anyone lie about
a dead person?
Then tell us the truth...
- Are you two brothers trying to...
- Sir!
Con the police?
Sir, no.
- He has nothing better to do.
- Wait, sir.
Hey, Ronny. What happened?
- Please come with me.
- Is the police with you?
Yes. Just come with me.
Who is she?
Come.
Aunty, tell them that
I come here every day.
Yes. He does.
You see, aunty.
He says this grave belongs to his Alisha.
But it belongs to this old lady -
Margaret.
I see him coming here every day
for the past few months.
- He sits in front of this grave.
- Oh!
I thought...
it was his mother's grave.
Margaret!
Oh!
- Hey...
- You're lying.
- How can you lie?
- Leave her. Let her go.
How can you lie?
Ronny, leave her.
What are you doing?
- Leave her.
- Leave me!
Bunch of liars all of you.
Why would I lie?
Where is Alisha?
Alisha...
- Ronny.
- Alisha!
Ronny.
I told you he hallucinates.
He's searching for
a girl that doesn't exist.
Let him look.
He'll either find the girl,
or the truth!
Don't know why...
But you look beautiful to me.
My new phone!
Oh no... I haven't even
paid the first EMI yet.
And you broke it.
Listen, I am really sorry.
It happens on the job.
Collateral damage.
Phone is my lifeline.
It's a matter of life and death.
How will I survive without my phone?
Stop crying over your phone.
A junkie was getting away
and you were busy making reels.
Gen Zs these days are like zombies.
if you stay off social media for a day...
It won't matter to anyone except you.
But it will matter to the society
if you don't do your
social responsibility!
Hey!
Can you two stop
this love connection of yours.
I am getting electrocuted.
Come on.
How long can you escape defensive forces?
And one more thing...
Men in uniform never
let civilians suffer any losses.
Understand?
They always think of their safety.
You'll get your lifeline back
when I get my next salary.
Until then, you can keep my phone.
I will deactivate my E-sim.
How are you going to return it?
When these eyes can locate the enemy--
I am sure finding
a phone will be easy.
Alisha, your phone's gone.
What about your sister?
Oh no!
Sister's going to kill me.
Alisha!
I just bought you a new phone.
What is wrong with you?
I've been trying to call you.
Why is your phone off?
It's broken.
He broke it.
Who did?
I know it was you.
You are very mischievous.
Did you break it?
Sister, please.
He showed me all his sides
in under fifteen minutes...
Anger. Bravery. Attitude.
And his statements hit like
a bombardment.
He's an officer of the Defence Sea-Forces.
Alisha, men are the biggest pain
in a woman's life.
Men keep one women in their heart,
another in their mind
and one in their house.
And they keep the likes of you
in delusion.
Our foster homes are always full
because of men like them.
You know you don't know.
You understand...
I don't want to know anything.
I just want my phone back.
Come on. Eat.
What are you listening?
You too.
By the way, sister.
When do these officers get their salary?
I don't know!
But I do know you won't get your salary,
because look at the time.
You're still not gone.
- Stop thinking about him.
- I am going.
You don't know anything about him.
I am going.
Bye.
Drink your milk, son.
You haven't been drinking
your milk for two days.
- Cheers.
Boss...
Who's the guy
that's lost the will to live?
That's the guy, boss.
Don't follow me.
Boss. He's the one.
Cheers.
In front of boss, no drinking.
I see... another one.
He'll open that one too.
And I'll grab it.
Me too.
Boss...
Hold on.
Hello...
Don't mistake me for a junk collector
collecting bottles.
Aren't you ashamed...
Calling a bazooka to kill a mosquito.
He's not a mosquito.
Do you have blood pressure?
Or take any other pill.
Finish your beer quickly.
Once Pali starts punching,
there are no breaks for drink...
Only broken bones.
Yeah.
Bro, listen I was on duty the other day
today is my day off, so...
I'm in no mood to fight.
But I am.
Because when someone got
in the mood,
I came to this world.
That's why I am always in the mood.
Okay, look.
I come here every day,
and I don't want to tear
this place apart, so...
Let's go outside.
He's reminded me of
my childhood days.
As a kid I would make similar excuses
when I knew I was going
to get a beating.
My son.
I feel you, bro.
Come out.
Bring him out.
Come on.
Hurry up.
You were giving me such attitude.
Look... that's my gang.
Boys, attack.
Go on!
Calm down!
It's just a broken right elbow.
It will be okay in three weeks.
Okay.
But your effort was a waste.
He's a lefty.
- Is it?
- Yes.
Sorry.
Come on.
Oh No!
It's just a broken knee.
In two weeks... it'll be okay.
You should be glad
that you won't have to
go down on your knees anymore.
Go on.
Beat him.
Did you come to fight him or scare me?
Get lost.
Idiot...
Beat him.
It's not over yet.
You did what you had to.
Now, it's my turn.
If you have...
any respect for old folks,
then please don't beat me up
in front of my boys
Give me your address.
I'll come there.
But you said,
you don't need a bazooka...
No, no, I said we don't need a grandpa!
Is it?
Look, I got to break something.
I know - you tell me what I can break.
Must break something?
I need this and this.
And this...
I know...
You can break my nose.
I can breathe even from my mouth.
- You're right about that.
- Thank you.
- Sir.
- Yes.
I've never seen someone beat a guy up
and then take him to the hospital.
Can you beat him up some more?
Otherwise... the guys
at the hospital won't take him in.
Is is your dad's college
that they won't admit me?
Sir...
Sir... I've admitted all of them.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Again on the phone.
This Gen Z will never learn.
Dr. Alisha. They are calling you.
Call the doctor.
- She's coming. She's coming.
- Why is she walking in slo-mo?
Dr Alisha.
Do you come here to attend the patients
or attend your phone?
Hold on.
There are other patients
like you who need me.
Without this phone,
I can not get to them on time.
That's why this phone is my lifeline.
Again with the phone.
Buried in your phone all day
with your head bowed down.
You? Doctor?
This is not rented.
I also have a degree.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't have called you Gen Z.
I tend to get a little serious on duty.
And we have to be calm,
or the patient gets serious.
Patient serious?
- Is my condition too serious?
- No...
You're bleeding.
Bleeding?
That rascal hit me really hard.
When did I get hurt?
It can be dangerous.
Dangerous?
Oh, God. I am doomed.
I am okay.
Is someone with you?
Family?
I was orphaned even before I was born.
Why don't you give me
the bad news once and for all.
Keep lying down.
Please come with me.
I am not going anywhere.
- Do what you want here.
- Stop. Okay.
You'll start bleeding
from the other nose.
Stop screaming.
By the way,
I am sorry for your phone.
It's getting fixed.
I'll return it as soon as I get it.
It's okay.
Now, let me just see this, please.
Five mm.
Any further and it could have
damaged the arteries.
You've got laceration at neck.
Don't worry.
Keep the moment of your neck limited.
And we're keeping you overnight
at the hospital
just to make sure that you're stable...
And to run some tests.
You'll be fine?
Are you sure?
Even doctors wear a uniform.
Please, just do as you've been told.
I'll be right back.
Listen, mister.
Is Dr Alisha coming?
She will
if there is an emergency.
Why didn't you say this before?
- What?
- Emergency!
Doctor!
Emergency!
If shedding blood is your thing,
you should donate some of it.
It can save someone's life.
Men in uniform are very responsible.
But you...
beat up people on the streets.
When we see injustice being done,
we don't care if we're on the streets
or the border?
And anyway...
there's something about me
that protects me from every danger.
Like my inner voice,
sixth sense, or...
Intuition!
Is it?
What happened to your intuition
when you got hurt?
It did help.
The guys I beat up,
I brought them to the hospital.
In the hospital, I saw you.
You saw my cut
and my intuition saved me.
Those who beat you up rarely
come back to help.
Wow!
Did your intuition also tell you
that you are going to get injected?
And you'll be seeing stars after that?
Listen... you're out of your mind.
It's not my mind, it's my heart.
Hi.
Ronny here.
What happened?
Did the bandage come off again?
I spoke to the guy fixing your phone.
You'll get it tomorrow.
Oh... so the guy fixing
my phone said this,
and not your intuition?
It's my intuition, not the internet.
Enough.
Sister Catherine says
there's no such thing as intuition.
Your sister Catherine is wrong.
Is it?
So connect with your intuition
and tell me where I am right now.
Okay, if I'm not wrong...
Balcony.
How?
And don't flirt with me,
because someone
behind you is listening.
Alisha, who are you talking to?
Oh shit!
Come see me tomorrow at 4 o'clock
at the cafe opposite the church...
And bring my phone, okay.
Bye.
What was that?
Whenever a young girl is talking
to a young guy,
someone's definitely eavesdropping.
Just like you were.
Brilliant, man.
You've been discharged.
Go... see your doctor.
Thank you.
Oh... Thank you.
By the way,
what's the scene with your intuition.
How can you be right every time?
Alisha, I can't lie to you.
My intuition--
You think you can get away with cheating?
You all will win against us? huh?
Take that, rascal!
Ronny!
Come on boys!
Beat the f*** out of them.
Hey, you ba***
You want to be a saviour?
Now save yourself, a****
I will blow your f****
head right here, right now!
Alisha, don't come closer.
He is drugged, he'll shoot!
Alisha.
Are you okay?
You're my first desire and my last...
I'm in love with you...
your love is important to me.
Without you, I'd be dead...
You're my reason to live.
Can't live a moment without you.
Can't live a moment without you...
No soul has witnessed what I hold.
The deity revered by all
resides within you.
My drowning heart...
found its shore in your gaze.
Can't live a moment without you.
You're my reason to be alive...
Tell me honestly.
Why did you point the gun
at you the other day?
Don't know.
Sixth sense. Intuition.
I just knew you'd save me.
I believe in you.
- But...
- Shh!
God knows everything.
On your path I lay my heart,
With every beat, your name I chant.
I climb the steps of love so high,
Learning its ropes as time goes by.
We look in each other's eyes,
Your anklets jingle as you pass by.
If I promise, I'll stay true,
Our love's beyond this world, beau.
Come Come
Can't live a moment without you.
Ever since you held my hand,
my lines of fate began to change.
Your words are worth more
than the entire world.
My love, you are my...
My love, you are my shining star.
Can't live without you.
You're my reason to be alive...
Can't live a moment without you.
Your heart belongs only to me...
Your... heart... belongs... only to me!
On your path I lay my heart,
With every beat, your name I chant.
I climb the steps of love so high,
Learning its ropes as time goes by.
We look in each other's eyes,
Your anklets jingle as you pass by.
If I promise, I'll stay true,
Our love's beyond this world, beau.
Come Come
O beloved, you are my only support,
O beloved...
Can't live a moment without you.
Hey, Ronny.
Is Jeetu here?
Alisha.
Girlfriend? Where?
Right there.
Where is she?
Where is the girl?
You said she is dead.
How?
Did you kill her?
Accident.
What accident?
Car accident.
If there was an accident... death...
Then...
Ambulance!
The ambulance driver
must have seen her.
So... are you the guy
who brought him to the hospital
after the accident?
Yes, sir. I did.
Now tell me,
was he alone
or with someone?
Sir, he was alone.
He was definitely alone.
Alisha used to live here?
Looks like a haunted mansion.
That Ronny is lying.
Your brother could be lying,
and even the ambulance driver...
but only one thing will never lie...
Camera!
This toll booth was near
the accident spot.
Will we find your Alisha here?
Stop.
That's my car, sir.
Zoom.
There is no girl in the car.
Alright, Angry young man,
I've had enough.
Now honestly tell me
what this is all about.
I won't stop until
I have found the truth.
Even if I have to give my life...
Or take one.
You think I am here to...
I did not become a cop just
to have tea.
Alright...
I want to know the truth
before I finish my tea.
The countdown begins.
Look, think about this with a calm mind.
Ronny.
Sir...
Kute, was the countdown
for telling the truth or running away?
For telling the truth.
- Then why did he run?
- Don't know, sir.
- Catch him!
- Yes, sir.
Come on!
Catherine! Catherine!
It's a good thing I found you.
- Who are you?
- Catherine!
How dare you touch me?
It's me Ronny. Alisha's friend.
Are you out of your mind?
Who's Alisha? Who's Ronny?
What are you saying?
I am Ronny, Catherine.
Don't you recognise me?
What are you saying?
Who are you? Are you crazy?
Leave me.
Help! He's crazy.
I don't know who he is.
Why are you lying?
- Ronny.
- Help!
Ronny... leave her.
What are you doing?
She is Alisha's sister Catherine.
Catherine, who?
I am Priyanka.
Sir, she's come here
for her father's final rites.
Quiet!
He is lying. She is Catherine.
No, sir. She is Priyanka.
Wait a minute.
Do you know her?
I've known her since her childhood.
She is Priyanka Shetty.
Listen up, if Alisha is Christian,
how can her sister be a Hindu?
Is this priest also lying now?
- Yes, they are all lying.
- Ronny, stop it man!
Ma'am, I am sorry.
My brother is slightly disturbed.
Please, go.
Take this lunatic
to the mental hospital...
Wait...
Sir.
I told him my collar was off limits.
- Sir...
- Sir, let him go...
Please let him go!
One more word
and I'll lock you up with him.
- I am requesting you, sir.
- No.
- Please hear me out.
Sir.
I wait for you on these streets,
day after day.
Even the sky seems to laugh at me.
My heart beats only for you.
Without you, it can't find peace.
You've changed me
in ways I never knew...
You showed me how to cry.
You showed me how...
Beloved, your love...
- Stay with me. - Showed me how to cry.
- How to cry...
- Don't leave me.
You are mine.
I am yours.
I love you, Alisha.
You showed me how to cry.
How to cry...
Beloved, your love...
Showed me how to cry.
How to cry...
Why did you bring me here?
Drugs or drink?
Ronny?
Ronny... you were hallucinating.
Blood...
If I am hallucinating,
where did the blood come from?
It's not a hallucination...
It's not a hallucination!
It's not! It's not!
Who are you?
Yo, I don't flinch
when the storm rolls deep
Eyes like fire,
ain't no time for sleep
Heart on war, every breath I feast
Uncage the rage, release the beast
Pulse like thunder,
strike with no grace
Claws in the dark, blood on my face
Ain't no peace
when I'm in that zone
Tear through steel,
break flesh, crack bone
Rage in my chest, beast in my soul,
Lose control, I go for the goal.
You hear that growl?
That's me unleashed
Warpath lit, I'm the rage,
I'm the beast.
Should I knock or come right in?
Got some booze.
Open the door.
Watch me fly like a glitch in the code,
All black suit, that's a hero mode,
Stare too long, you might just fold,
Heart too pure but my soul too cold.
I don't flex, but I will throw hands,
No side kick, I don't need no band,
Don't need luck, just a slick game plan,
Snap so hard they forgot
where they stand.
Hey! Get up!
Is anyone alive?
Huh? Hey!
Get up!
Hey! Get up a***.
Are you alive? Get up!
Get up!
Is anyone alive?!
[Coughs]
Hey... Stay alive.
Look at me. Stay alive.
Quiet. Quiet.
Come here!
Look.
Tell me.
Who do you see?
Tell me!
- You.
- Yes.
Who else?
Hurry up.
Girl.
Read what's written.
Ronny and Alisha!
Who is controlling everybody?
Why was everybody lying to me?
Who has the influence and money...
to wipe out Alisha's existence?
Who's really pulling the strings?
Who went so far just to
get me out of the way?
Who turned everyone against me?
Why is everyone following his orders?
Who's Alisha? Who's Ronny?
He was alone, sir!
That's his mother's grave.
You were hallucinating.
There is no girl in the car.
There is no girl called Alisha.
It's just your imagination.
Even my brother's part of the plan.
Why did Jeetu lie to me?
Jeetu!
Where is Jeetu?
Hey, Jeetu.
Where are you?
Jeetu.
Jeetu has a gun?
Why?
Pick up the phone, Jeetu.
Pick up the phone.
Jeetu, I am coming.
If you don't tell me
the truth this time,
I will kill you.
I will kill you!
Jeetu!
[Coughs]
Jeetu...
Go away, Ronny.
Ronny, no.
Ronny!
Jeetu!
Leave me and run!
[Shrieks]
Ronny!
Ronny.
Jeetu!
They are dangerous people, Ronny.
They paid me to lie about Alisha
and save your life.
They also gave me a gun...
If I ever think about telling you
the truth,
I should shoot myself.
Tell me his name!
Go away. Run, Ronny.
Jeetu?
Jeetu!
Get up, Jeetu.
I won't let anything happen to you.
You kept looking out for me,
and I resented you.
- No, Jeetu.
- Save yourself.
- Leave, Ronny.
- Go away, brother. Please.
- Jeetu, no!
[Flute plays]
Jeetu?
Jeetu.
No no no...
No, Jeetu, please don't leave me.
Don't leave me...
Jeetu, no.
- Ronny... take care, my brother.
- No Jeetu, no.
No, Jeetu.
Forgive me.
Sorry.
Talk to me...
Talk to me, brother.
I'm still here.
Jeetu, get up, please.
Talk to me.
Don't leave me.
Open your eyes.
Please.
Don't leave me, Jeetu.
Jeetu, please.
[Laughs]
We'll meet again.
Because I'm not allowed
to kill you... yet!
I knew this would happen.
Poor Jeetu's gone.
Sir.
Jeetu, I am coming.
If you don't tell me the truth this time,
I will kill you.
I will kill you!
That rascal fled
after killing his brother.
Where will we find him now?
I know... where.
Laila. Laila. Laila. Laila--
Lai... la!
Spread your web, web, web--
'Spread it.
Laila. Laila. Laila. Laila--
Lai... la!
Spread your web, web, web--
'Spread it.
With my name tattooed on their arm
and my pictured tucked in their purse...
They swarm around me like wild fans,
Like old-school lovers lost in a trance.
Their eyes drift here,
but aim's completely off.
I've only one heart to give away.
who should I give it to?
In this crowd of desperate lovers,
I am the only Laila.
Gotta sneak past all these watchful eyes,
I'm getting calls from back home.
Everyone's trying to play the hero,
but I need a villain to save my life.
I wouldn't even show my face
in front of them.
In this crowd of desperate lovers,
I am the only Laila.
Hey Laila...
how many heroes are there?
Laila. Laila. Laila. Laila--
Lai... la!
Spread your web, web, web--
'Spread it.
I've only one heart to give away.
who should I give it to?
In this crowd of desperate lovers,
I am the only Laila.
Laila. Laila. Laila. Laila--
Lai... la!
Spread your web, web, web--
'Spread it.
I've only one heart to give away.
who should I give it to?
In this crowd of desperate lovers,
Laila is stuck.
HBP - High Blood Pressure.
Not me.
I have that effect on people.
What do you want from me?
Where is Ronny?
I don't know.
My memory isn't great
Wha...
You got his name tattooed on your arm,
and keep his picture in your purse...
And you claim you don't remember.
Maybe this will jog your memory.
I said I don't remember.
Now... did that bring back your memory?
He comes, meets me and leaves.
Why are you looking for him?
I can't tell you.
Maybe this will jog your memory.
I said I can't tell you.
Now... did that bring back your memory?
He's on the run
after murdering his brother.
He cannot kill his brother.
Is it?
He loves his brother a lot.
Then why is he on the run?
He's not running...
He's searching.
He's looking for someone
who doesn't exist.
And killing those who do.
Leave him alone.
That's not possible.
And now?
Oh wow!
I will save him. HBP promise.
Look... even God's scared of those
who have nothing to lose.
If he's done nothing,
who is he scared of?
Come on. Call him.
Are you sure he'll be alright?
Do I have your word?
Like I said - HBP promise.
Call him, Laila. Call him.
- Hello?
- Ronny...
Get rid of your phone and SIM.
Police are looking for you.
You were right, HBP.
Even God's scared of those
who have nothing to lose...
But not someone
who's already lost everything.
Drastic, fantastic, bombastic...
But remember...
I'll be back soon... to arrest you.
Until then,
keep doing...
Let's go.
Come on.
You okay?
I want to tell you something
about sister Catherine.
Nice to meet you.
Come on, brother let's play!
Let's go, brother.
-Bye.
You okay?
You sure you're okay?
I want to tell you something
about sister Catherine.
She does not want me to meet...
- Alisha.
- Ronny.
Alisha.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me. Alisha.
I...
love... you...
No...
Ronny...
You were hallucinating.
Why was everyone lying?
What was she trying
to tell me about Catherine?
Pandit ji.
Why did you call me here?
I told you not to contact me.
You know I can get in big trouble.
I clearly told you...
Where are you going, Pandit ji?
No no no...
Who is forcing you lie?
Even forced you to change your religion.
Hurry up and tell me
or I will turn you to dust.
I was threatened!
By Paulo.
No, no. No...
Come here.
You better keep Alisha
and Ronny apart.
Otherwise, this time,
it was just the bus.
Next time the children will be in it.
Alisha, I don't like this guy.
Stay away from him.
For everyone's sake.
They are dangerous people.
They have eyes on me 24/7.
[Flute plays]
Ronny!
I am Olivia.
Pratistha!
Girlfriend?
Pratistha. Olivia!
Ronny.
Two names. Two identities!
Which face will be exposed today?
Paulo's friend or
the traitor who turned on me?
Paulo's phone.
You called him several times.
Ronny, I can explain--
I thought girls like
you had some rules.
We're the only ones
who play by the rules
Which I broke... for you.
Because I started to fall for you.
I want to kill you right now!
Ronny...
I wait for you on these streets,
day after day.
Even the sky seems to laugh at me.
My heart beats only for you-
Without you, it can't find peace.
You've changed me
in ways I never knew...
You showed me how to cry.
You showed me how...
Beloved, your love...
Showed me how to cry.
Paulo...
Olivia's betrayed us.
Ronny will find out everything.
Kill Ronny.
What?
I will explain Chacko!
Kill him.
I'm glad you gave me your heart...
Feels like a wish I made came true.
You've become a part of me.
With you, I finally feel whole.
Every moment without you feels
- like something's missing.
- Ronny.
No.
You cannot die.
Not you.
Your prayer has been answered.
No, no,
not at all.
She's alive...
Alisha is alive!
Alisha... is alive.
Alisha!
This body been shaped just
for your eyes.
Every inch of me,
made to mesmerise.
I once lit up the skies
like the moonlight,
But I was brought down
to earth for you alone.
This body been shaped
just for your eyes.
Every inch of me,
made to mesmerise.
I once lit up the skies
like the moonlight,
But I was brought down
to earth for you.
Lovers praise the curve of my smile,
They swoon at the grace of my step....
They're obsessed with me,
But I've been guarded from evil eye .
Kept away from prying eyes
only for you.
I once lit up the skies
like the moonlight,
But I was brought down
to earth for you.
This body been shaped
just for your eyes.
Every inch of me,
made to mesmerise.
I once lit up the skies
like the moonlight,
But I was brought down
to earth for you,
Ronny...
Who are you?
Don't... come close to me.
No...
I want to get out of here.
You are mistaken.
Where's Ronny?
Same voice...
Same face.
Same eyes...
But...
minus the fear.
Avantika.
I will never touch you.
Please. Let me go.
Okay I'll spare you.
Which hand of yours touched me?
Chacko!
Darling.
I think he touched you.
You are the only one who's ever touched me...
and now this hand.
So I brought it along.
He was a bloody lefty.
What? Was he a lefty?
Even his father was lefty.
Look, Chacko.
Life is like a puzzle,
there's always a piece missing.
And that one piece in my life - is you.
Tell me, Chacko.
When will you marry me?
Do you know how old you are?
In this lifetime, love is important.
Not the age you get it in.
Don't get poetic with me, baby.
Chacko...
I want to live with you
till one life falls short.
Then even if death embraces me,
I won't complaint.
I will never let you die.
Say it...
Will you keep loving me
like this always...
Till death do us apart?
I will snatch you back
from God himself.
Do you know who he is...
Does he know who I am?
Chacko... my wedding gown is ready.
Chacko will marry me!
Love is patient.
Love is kind.
Therefore what God has joined together,
let no one separate.
Does anyone have any obj...
Dogs and cats come in packs,
but a lion stands alone and tall,
Avantika.
Chacko.
Never with toys, I've always played
with weapons and all.
My blood runs hot, my ego's strong,
I carry a 47 with pride,
My enemies beg as mafia's related to me
and always by my side.
I don't spare the ones I see,
one look, and they're done by me,
My guns don't stop,
putting holes through all, on a spree.
Bang-bang-bang,
My bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang-bang,
My bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang,
You're no match for me for
I'm built strong undeniably,
Your screams and my shots
both tear the air differently.
As long as I breathe,
I'll shoot to kill for fun,
This life's a villain's role,
you won't survive what I've begun.
I can burn with sweat,
my roar brings fear,
I'm fierce and wild,
that's why you should stay clear.
My eyes are locked,
I never miss the aim,
These guns aren't bought,
They're part
of the family's name.
Not every matter
to my boss is escalated by me,
My guns don't stop,
putting holes through all, on a spree.
Bang-bang-bang,
my bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang-bang,
my bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang,
Bang-bang-bang,
my bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang-bang,
my bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Avantika.
No...
No!
It's closed.
Why?
Because God is on leave.
What?
What is God's role
in the devil's love story?
Tell me...
I want to know!
Everyone kneels before You...
But out of fear.
Fear!
Not faith.
You want Chacko to kneel before You?
Chacko...
will kneel before You!
He will do it for Avantika.
He will...
Chacko's kneeling before You!
What do You want from me?
In a life filled with bloodshed,
she was my only respite.
She was like me.
All my life I kept to myself.
But never felt alone
when she was around.
God...
please give her back to me.
Please, God!
Please give her back to me God.
Please God...
Please!
Are you listening?
Give her back to me!
If you let me turn into a monster,
humans won't be safe anymore.
God...
Let's make a deal.
Give me back my Avantika,
and I will spare this world of yours.
Right?
Or else...
I'll destroy your world in such a way...
And turn in into a living nightmare.
That everyone will be stunned.
Scared?
You should be!
Undo it.
Undo it...
Undo it!
Sent her back so soon, God!
Thank you, my Lord.
Will you marry me?
Open the door.
God sent you back.
You're my Avantika.
No.
Don't come close to me.
Romeo and Juliet.
Heer-Ranjha...
And after Laila-Majnu -
the only love story that matters...
is Chacko and Avantika's.
I lost you once.
I can't lose you again.
I don't love your body...
I love this face of yours.
Marry me.
No! This is not possible!
I only love Ronny!
Forget him. Get over him.
Only I exist in your life now.
Me!
Boys like Ronny mistake lust for love.
Men can change their habit...
But not their character.
But he cannot forget me
as long as he is alive.
If you have unwavering faith
in your love story,
I don't have an ounce
of doubt in mine.
Ronny can never forget me.
He will...
He will forget you.
Sooner or later...
Maybe in a week, a month.
But he will forget you.
Forget weeks or months...
If he forgets me in a year,
I will marry you.
And as you said...
you don't love my body.
Let's put it to test.
Remember this day...
8th September.
You have such unwavering faith in him?
You won't understand.
Because this is about love.
Women are unbeaten in love...
And undefeated in hatred.
All these cameras in the city,
and he doesn't show up in anyone.
Which hole is this rat hiding in?
Where is he?
Hey... catch him!
Wait!
What catch him?
He's an atom bomb...
walked right in to explode.
Let him come.
Welcome.
You had trouble believing
she even existed...
But Alisha's alive.
But I don't know where she is.
Come with me.
Our all plans have failed.
Ronny knows the truth
about Alisha being alive.
We told him she's dead
and also showed him her grave.
But he didn't forget her.
We made him hallucinate.
It didn't work.
We made Olivia enter his life.
But he still didn't forget.
I tried to kill him.
I failed.
Tomorrow is the final day of our bet...
How are we going to prove
that Ronny has forgotten Alisha?
Do you have any plan, big brother?
Boom!
Ronny!
Hey, shortie.
You turned my police station
into a dump.
Who is going to clean all this up?
You?
And stop yelling Ronny.
This is a police station,
not a take away centre--
where you can come, order,
take your food and leave.
I want Ronny.
I want Ronny too!
If you wanted to make friends,
then why come dressed for battle?
Friends never quarrel, man.
Relax. Cool.
I don't want any trouble.
I wanted money... I got it.
Your parcel is ready...
Take away.
Ronny... see you again
in next lifetime.
Let's go.
Today is the final day of our bet.
I want to show you something.
He's gotten over you!
I want to meet him.
Now!
You're my first desire and my last...
I'm in love with you...
your love is important to me.
Without you, I'd be dead...
You're my reason to live.
Can't live a moment without you.
Can't live a moment without you...
I missed you, Ronny.
Are you alright?
Do you know what they did?
What?
They showed me a picture
of you with some girl
and thought--
What did you think?
I'd believe you?
I believe in my Ronny.
I knew Ronny would
never do such a thing...
It's true, Alisha.
No.
No, no, no, I knew it was a lie.
I believe in my love.
I believe in Ronny.
- Ronny can never...
- It's true.
It's true.
You did it.
I thought you're dead--
You thought I was dead?
Every moment...
I waited for you like a lunatic.
And took you only a minute
to forget me.
I lost, Ronny...
To myself, my love and this bet.
You thought... I was dead.
I wish I was dead.
I hate you, Ronny.
I will never forgive you.
I hate you.
Leave me!
I will marry Chacko!
Right now!
Tell him.
You get it.
You betrayed me, Ronny.
You betrayed me.
I'll never forgive you.
[paulo laughs]
Good boy.
You did exactly as I told you.
Alisha's been safe with us for a year.
If you didn't listen to me,
I would have killed her.
You saved my sister-in-law Alisha,
but who's going to save you?
My brother suffered
for 365 days because of him.
He must suffer for 365 minutes.
Torture him and then...
You lost the bet.
Now you'll be my Avantika.
Tired so soon?
There's a lot more coming your way.
My Alisha is alive.
I will move heaven
and earth to get to her.
Ronny, your story is emotional.
While most cops have traitors
in the ranks,
I ended up with a whelp.
Kute. Bet he's already squealed
your name to his boss.
Go tear them apart!
I've said it before...
What you call torture...
is warm up for me.
I just had to meet Alisha.
And see her alive.
Get Ready to Fight.
Let's go.
I need you.
Alisha!
Sir, Ronny killed Paulo.
Now you realise
what it feels like to lose a brother.
Dogs and cats come in packs,
but a lion stands alone and tall,
Never with toys, I've always played
with weapons and all.
My blood runs hot, my ego's strong,
I carry a 47 with pride,
My enemies beg as mafia's related to me
and always by my side.
I don't spare the ones I see,
one look, and they're done by me,
My guns don't stop,
putting holes through all, on a spree.
Bang-bang-bang,
My bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang-bang,
My bullets tear through flesh,
I leave holes in the chest.
Bang-bang-bang,
Avantika, shoot him.
Shoot him in the heart.
I told you, betraying comes
naturally to him.
Shoot him Avantika.
Remember what I said...
Women are unbeaten in love...
And undefeated in hatred.
I am Alisha.
Alisha!
Ronny and I were always together.
I believe in my love.
I believe in Ronny.
- Ronny can never...
- It's true.
Trust me!
I'm with you. Ronny.
Guns can kill humans...
Not the devil.
Ask Him.
Fear, fear, fear.
I knew you would save me.
Chacko, I want to live with you
till one life falls short.
Get Ready to Fight.
There's no warrior born quite like you,
No one else stands brave
and true like you,
Forever we'll hold in memory's stream,
The rivers of blood that forged our dream.
There's no warrior born quite like you,
No one else stands brave
and true like you,
Forever we'll hold in memory's stream,
The rivers of blood that forged our dream.
Get Ready to Fight.
Those who stand before us,
be it ninety or ninety-five,
They'll dance today
in death's cold light.
Blood will flow like water's stream,
Weapons will strike,
History's pages tell of such fights, /i>
Dark nights, dark cells,
deception's heights,
This is battle, where all pay the price,
here no one stops or plays nice.
Start the battle, fierce the flame,
This is the game of fate,
let find out who ends up dead, my mate.
Fear, fear, fear.
Ronny.
Listen to me, Ronny.
He'll come back and kill us, Ronny.
Kill him, Ronny.
He will abduct me again.
He will separate us again, Ronny.
Just kill him!
He's a psycho!
You will love me this much, won't you?
Untill death?
You... cannot be my Avantika.
I am Alisha.
Avantika!
You haven't understood, Chacko.
One thing about love is that...
It can never be stolen.
You too?
There's a thin line between
need and necessity.
Alisha was your need
for me she is necessary.
Not every lover is a villain.
Can't take my eyes off you...
No one else shines like
you do by my side.
Can't take my eyes off you...
No one else shines like
you do by my side.
You're on my mind...
everything else just fades away.
Can't tell you why...
you seem so cute.
Can I talk about you...
Figure out what your eyes are
trying to say?
Can we move forward...
Just wanna know,
can I fall in love with you?
Eyes sparkle like diamonds.
Shine like the moon,
gorgeous like angels.
Pull me closer, save my life.
You're my only reason to stay alive.
Come closer... closer...
let this saga begin.
Can't tell you why...
you seem so cute.
Don't want to know
what your eyes try to say...
Don't want to struggle in love.
You have a way with words...
Don't want to lose control hearing you.
Tell me what to do... what to do...
everywhere I look, I see you.
Can't tell you why...
you seem so cute.
Roses are red, violets are blue
My love, where are you from?
Tell me... Tell me...
Roses are red, violets are blue.
My love, where are you from?
Tell me... Tell me...
Can't tell you why...
you seem so cute.
You're my first desire and my last...
I'm in love with you...
your love is important to me.
Without you, I'd be dead...
You're my reason to live.
Can't live a moment without you.
On your path I lay my heart,
With every beat, your name I chant.
I climb the steps of love so high.
Learning its ropes as time goes by.
We look in each other's eyes,
Your anklets jingle as you pass by.
If I promise, I'll stay true,
Our love's beyond this world, beau.
Come Come
O beloved, you are my only support,
O beloved
Can't live a moment without you.
You're my first desire and my last...
I'm in love with you...
your love is important to me.
Without you, I'd be dead...
You're my reason to live.
Can't live a moment without you.
You're my reason to be alive...
Can't live a moment without you...
No soul has witnessed what I hold.
The deity revered by all
resides within you.
My drowning heart...
found its shore in your gaze.
Can't live a moment without you.
O beloved, you are my only support,
Ever since you held my hand,
my lines of fate began to change.
Your words are worth more
than the entire world.
My love, you are my...
My love, you are my shining star.
Can't live without you.
You're my reason to be alive...
Can't live a moment without you.
Your heart belongs only to me...
Your... heart... belongs... only to me!
I've laid out my heart at your feet.
It's not about the body...
You dwell in my soul.
Can't live a moment without you.
O beloved, you are my only support,
On your path I lay my heart,
With every beat, your name I chant.
I climb the steps of love so high.
Learning its ropes as time goes by.
We look in each other's eyes,
Your anklets jingle as you pass by.
If I promise, I'll stay true,
Our love's beyond this world, beau.
Come Come
O beloved, you are my only support,
O beloved
Can't live a moment without you.